



Yukhnovskiy Ilya

Male, 42 years old, born on 18 February 1978

+7 (902) 7800807 — preferred means of communication juhnowski@gmail.com Skype: iyukhnov

Reside in: Nizhny Novgorod

Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia Ready to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

StartUP Manager /Business(System) analyst / Architect of Cloud Microservices

4 000

IT, Internet, Telecom

- Software Development
- Engineer

Employment: project work, full time

Work schedule: remote working, flexible schedule, full day, shift schedule

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 18 years 10 months

May 2020 — till now 10 months

startuper

analyst / startup manager

SberUP business ideas - BA:

- 1)SberAtom https://github.com/juhnowski/SberAtom
- 2)Finteh Integration (MyMuseum) https://github.com/juhnowski/finteh_integration

Quantum nuclear computing (QNC) - StartUP BA/SA/OOA/OOD

- 1) Quantum calculations on currents inside a packet of an accelerated particle beam https://github.com/juhnowski/MarkovsChains
- 2)Use of Ionizing Radiation Sources in Quatum Information Systems https://github.com/juhnowski/NQCApplication

Analytics projects - BA

- 1) PSA neuron networks MedicalAI https://github.com/juhnowski/MedicalAI
- 2) Agile Next analysis of business processes in software development https://github.com/juhnowski/agile next
- 3) StartUP for 2021 SberUP's season ArtShare https://github.com/juhnowski/art_share

DS Projects + BA/SA/OOA/OOD

- 1) Ising's DS visulisation https://github.com/juhnowski/DS_Visualisation
- 2) Weather ETL project https://github.com/juhnowski/weather backend

UI/UX prototype + BA/SA/OOA/OOD

- 1) Startup for business school https://github.com/juhnowski/amonita
- 2) Startup for 2020 season SberUP https://github.com/juhnowski/burntreatmentdevice
- 3) Medical startups for SberUP's 2020 seasons:

https://sites.google.com/view/burntreatmentdevice/home

https://sites.google.com/site/telemrt/home

https://sites.google.com/site/dyrodssturtup/home

https://sites.google.com/view/arduino-eeg/home

4) Startups for 2019 SberUP's season

Octopus

Eletric Charge Stations

5) Startups for 2018 SberUP's season

Docophila - Final

Software development projects:

- 1) Ising model with various simplifications https://github.com/juhnowski/comp_ph
- 2) Solving the Schrödinger Equation for Different Variants with Animated Results

https://youtu.be/CR5dHD-8fWY

https://youtu.be/I6Ruy711PzQ

https://youtu.be/CR5dHD-8fWY

https://youtu.be/ejjM4CIL4V4

https://github.com/juhnowski/shred

- 3)NQC UI frontend prototype https://github.com/juhnowski/qiskit
- 4) Startup for 2020 season SberUP SberOkkoTarget https://github.com/juhnowski/cv_render

July 2018 — till now 2 years 8 months

Sberbank

www.sbrf.ru

Head of Direction (CIB, CC360)

Developer "My Account"

EFS - Workplace of the Client Manager)

Development of visualization tools for the planning and economic department of the Volga-City opercenter

Organization of internships and training

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vrwuEGkuVXQ

Work with contractors

Participation in job fairs and career promotion in IT specialists and hackathon organizations

Microservice and Cloud Architecture Resource Training GoogleCloud, Google App Engine, Google

Kubernetes Engine

Startups as part of Sber # UP

Docophila - contextual document search service

A backend for Java, Spring, ElasticSearch with a neural network for recognizing text from Google was developed

Water Ticket Service

Microservice architecture SpringData, SCCS, Spring Cloud, Kafka, Mongo, Zoo, Eureka, Docker, Kubernetes

Docophila 2

Backend - Python, Django, SQLite / PostgreSQL, Sphinx

Court-SMEV3

Software development for the organization of electronic document management at the regional level (Volga Volga Federal District) in SMEV3 between the Regional Court, World Courts, FSSP and PJSC Sberbank

Mobile applications

MWP business intelligence on Kotlin for Android + Javalin

Data Science - Python (NLP) + ElasticSearch (BigData Visualization)

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hXqwFchEbGY

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4lwqjfWcb6o

https://www.youtube.com/wat ch? v = V3u5haZat58

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J8reu0p3GUc

Utility for system administrators

Shop window prototype

Java Installer

Pattern recognition

BPM applications

Tibco, Camunda - simulation of BPM processes for fintech

December 2016 — July 2018 1 year 8 months

Sbrebank-Technology

Nizhny Novgorod

Head of IT Systems Development

Backend: (Java + Spring) + Frontend: (React Native + Objective-C) Prototyping / Extra-Project Activities: Clojure, Elasticsearch, Python,

Developed Objective-C training for JS Front End developers - task code on github.

December 2015 — May 2016 6 months

Individual entrepreneurship / private practice / freelance

Moscow

Project manager

- 1) Creating an internal JEE system development process
 - tomcat
 - Spring, Hibernate, JPA, EJB, JSP, REST, XML, JDBC, Freemarker
 - Implementation of Jenkins, GitHUB
- 2) OOA / OOD management system
 - C, Java, Python, JavaScript
- 3) Ethernet protocol development
 - http://synchrocom-proto.com/

March 2012 — February 2014 2 years

Folio-auto LLC

Moscow

Head of IT

Project management (IT component) in several areas:

- online game development (Backend Java, FrontEnd WebGL + JavaScript)
- robotic complex
- data monitoring in a complex human-machine system
- development of a system for monitoring fast realtime processes

C, C++, Java, Python + Math + Physics

July 2011 — February 2012 8 months

Буревестник, ОАО ЦНИИ

Nizhny Novgorod, www.burevestnik.com

Business Analyst

Analysis of the ministry's requirements for new weapons, development of business requirements and requirements for system integration of contractors' products

Development of a scientific library for the calculation of ballistics C, C++, GSL

Development of architecture and prototype control system

May 2010 — June 2011 1 year 2 months

LLC Teleka (Kyocera, Samsung, Verizon)

Nizhny Novgorod

Leading Software Engineer

Kyocera Wirless - Contour, FrameworkView

Samsung - work at the customer in Korea, bug fixing Linux, Android, Nvidia drivers

Verizon - Android Customization

March 2010 — May 2010 3 months

Мера НН

Nizhny Novgorod

IT engineer

writing demos for Nortel call center

December 2009 — February 2010 3 months

ЗАО "АЦЭТП"

Nizhny Novgorod

Programmer

Writing a workflow system for the Federal Antimonopoly Service C # MSSQL

August 1999 — May 2009 9 years 10 months

Shield LLC, Kond LLC, Kont LLC

Nizhny Novgorod Oblast

по совместительству

Design, development, conclusion of contracts, installation and commissioning of several generations of an enterprise access control system and video surveillance systems. The developed product is installed at private and state enterprises of Nizhny Novgorod, Kirov, Chuvash, Vladimir, Moscow region.

November 2007 — February 2009 1 year 4 months

FORUS Bank CJSC

Nizhny Novgorod, www.forusbank.ru

Front Office Project Manager

Maintenance of ABS "BISKVIT", writing scripts on 4GL, design and development of front-office for lending on J2EE Weblogic (document management, credit history, CRM)

July 2003 — November 2007 4 years 5 months

OOO "Тэлма" (Motorola, Vodafone, TIM)

Nizhny Novgorod

software engineer, marketing specialist

Java, at the time of dismissal, a marketing specialist in the Motorola department (Italia, Turin).

The work consisted of analyzing the current state of the mobile technology market and writing requirements for new products, taking into account available resources at two Russian sites (St. Petersburg and Nizhny Novgorod).

Practical knowledge of CMM and CMMI.

Motorola design and development API:

- J2ME Multimedia Player API
- J2ME SyncML API
- J2ME Push to X
- MSRP
- Aplex JVM support
- Platforma 2000, JVM development
- P2k support, Java App from e380 to RAZR Vodafone customization of Motorola phones:
- J2ME Screen Saver
- J2ME Vodafone Extension Framework TIM support for third party developers:
- Turbo Call music content distribution, DRM.

August 2001 — July

2003 2 years

Petrocommerce, Commercial Bank

Nizhny Novgorod, www.pkb.ru

Chief Specialist

ABS support RS-Bank, Diasoft client-bank, design and development of specialized software.

September 1999 — August 2001 2 years

OJSC "Afrikantov OKBM"

Russia

Engineer

Development of a probabilistic safety analysis program

Education

Higher

2001 Нижегородский Государственный Технический Университет

Ядерные реакторы и Энергетические Установки, магистр техники и технологии по направлению

техническая физика

1999 Нижегородский Государственный Технический Университет

Дополнительного образования, Информационный менеджмент

Professional development, courses

JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY

Coursera, The R Programming Environment

2020 **IBM**

Courcera, Coursera, Programming a Quantum Computer with Qiskit - IBM SDK

2020 University of Geneva

Courcera, Particle Physics

2020 Гонконгский университет науки и технологий

Courcera, Business English: Basics

2019 JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY Coursera, Building a Data Science Team 2019 University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign Coursera, Cloud Computing Applications, Part 2: Big Data and Applications in the Cloud 2019 University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign Coursera, Data Visualization 2019 University of Maryland, College Park Coursera, Криптография 2019 Google Cloud Coursera, Reliable Cloud Infrastructure: Design and Process 2019 Google Cloud Coursera, Building Scalable Java Microservices with Spring Boot and Spring Cloud 2019 Google Cloud Coursera, Reliable Cloud Infrastructure: Design and Process 2019 **Google Cloud** Coursera, Architecting with Google Kubernetes Engine 2019 Google Cloud Coursera, Architecting with Google Kubernetes Engine: Production 2019 Google Cloud Coursera, Architecting with Google Kubernetes Engine: Workloads 2018 Google Сбербанк, Бизнес Класс (бизнес моделирование, маркетинг, исследование рынка и потребительского поведения, продажи и управление сервисом.) 2015 Методы тестирования QTest НИИТ, свидетельство о дополнительном профессиональном образовании 2014 Промышленный сетевой протокол Ethernet Power Link МИРЭА, повышение квалификации 2012 Efficient development with CoDeSys V3 PROLOG, training course 2011 Язык визуализирования (UML) НИИТ, свидетельство о дополнительном профессиональном образовании 1997 Информационный менеджмент Нижегородский Государственный Технический Университет, специалист Key skills Languages Russian — Native English — B2 — Upper Intermediate

Skills

UML Spring Framework SQL JavaScript Linux Android Kotlin Java PowerShell Bash REST Системный анализ Objective-C Python MongoDB ElasticSearch Kibana

Driving experience

Own car

Driver's license category B

Further information

About me

I propose to join the joint startup to the SberUp accelerator

My career as a startup and inventor began at the institute and continues to this day. Four times winner of a personal Khariiton's scholarship, participant of 4 seasons of SberUp, was the founder of several start-up projects: J&K Softlabs, Odacon, Phreebie

The success of my startups is guaranteed by a deep IT background.

Analyst skills: UML, BPM(BPMS, Camunda, Tibco), RUP, Jira, Confluence, IBM Rational (DOORS,

ROSE), MS Visio

Methodology: Agile/Scrum DS: R-studio, Tableau

Cloud

Docker, Kubernetes, Kafka, Cloud Pub / Sub, Bigtable, Cloud SQL, App Engine

C/C++Stack

Conan - package manager

RabbitMQ - messaging

JSON - message format + sha256 encryption

OpenCV - analysis and processing of decoded frames

ffmpeg / libav - encoding, decoding video streams

git - version control

python - system tests

googletest - unit tests

cmake - build the project

C ++ - 14, plans to skip 17 and go to 20

active use of algorithm, stream, multithreading

now refactoring to FP style

experience with cuda and assembler

JVM Stack

Spring Boot, Spring Cloud, Spring Secure, Spring Data, Spring MVC

BEA WebLogic, Payara, Google Cloud Platform,

Clojure

Kotlin (Android)

NoSQL Stack

Firebase

Elastic(Kibana)

MongoDB

XML,XSD,WSDL

SQL Stack

Oracle,

Postgres,

MySQL,

Microsoft SQL Server

Progress(4GL)

SQLite

Python

Django

SciPy

NumPy

....

Functional Stack

Haskell

Mercury

R-lang